{"metadata":{"generator":"Captivate","generatorVersion":"10.0.0","schemaVersion":"","author":"author","title":"","description":"project description","email":"author@company.com","website":"www.company.com","tags":"","thumbnail":"","source":"assets","durationInFrames":2322,"frameRate":30,"totalSlides":8,"width":1080,"height":627,"responsive":false,"scalable":true,"launchFile":"index.html"},"contentStructure":[{"id":"Image_3","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_3","roles":{}},{"id":"SmartShape_1","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_1","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_1","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1","title":"Population Health: Public Health ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Line_1","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Line_1","roles":{}},{"id":"Text_Caption_2","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_2","title":"This sub-module develops the ability of the participant to assess characteristics within a community that may lead to increased risk of disease ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_3","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_3","title":"Length: 5 minutes ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_2","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_2","title":"Start ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9938","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Start ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9949","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Start ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_2","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_2","roles":{}},{"id":"Text_Caption_4","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_4","title":"This CE program was developed for the following grant: Primary Care Nurse Practitioner Preceptor Development Program (PC-NP-PDP)  HRSA GRANT # D09HP29976 Principal Investigator:  D. Hallas PhD, CPNP, PMHS, FAANP ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_32","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_32","title":"1 / 8 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide9971","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_3","SmartShape_1","Text_Caption_1","Text_Caption_2","Text_Caption_3","SmartShape_2","si9938","si9949","Image_2","Text_Caption_4","Text_Caption_32"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide9971"}}},{"id":"si15875","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si15886","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si15892","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si15905","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"f ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si15919","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"____ ____ ____ ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19298","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"g ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_5","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_5","title":"Population Health: Public Health ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_25","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_25","title":"Link: CDC - Intoduction to Public Health ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_33","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_33","title":"2 / 8 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_44","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_44","title":"Click here if video does not load ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Web_2","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Web_2","roles":{}},{"id":"Slide5186","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"Public Health Definition","thumbnail":"","children":["si15875","si15886","si15892","si15905","si15919","si19298","Text_Caption_5","Text_Caption_25","Text_Caption_33","Text_Caption_44"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide5186"}}},{"id":"si19309","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"g ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_6","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_6","title":"Population Health: Public Health ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_34","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_34","title":"3 / 8 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_40","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_40","title":"Evolving Case Study   ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_41","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_41","title":"Ms. R. is an African American woman presenting with her 18 month old in your pediatric practice for a healthy visit. The child has always been in the 20th percentile for weight gain with primary meals coming from formula made from tap water in the home. The mom reports that now that the child is eating table food they seem less hungry and more irritable. The child’s weight today has dropped to the 15th percentile.    The child’s developmental screening reveals some subtle motor and cognitive delays. The child seems clumsy and has difficulty following a simple one-word direction.   You, as the NP, reassure the mom that each child develops at their own pace. You suggest that you will conduct another developmental screen at the next visit. You advise the mom on nutrition for toddlers. She makes an appointment with you for two year visit and has accepted this plan of care.   After the visit, the mom shares with other mom’s on the playgroud at the housing complex her child’s issues. The housing complex is much less expensive that other federally controlled affordable housing residences permitting these  families that are living at 185 % of poverty guidelines  to live here for generations. Consequently the properties are poorly maintained with requests for repairs going unanswered.  Moms of other toddler-aged children also reflect that their children are in the lower weight percentile and have been given nutrition information from their health care providers (hcp’s). They continuing discussing feeding habits and discover that they all use heirloom pottery bowls that they ate from as children with their children. They also mention that they have noticed that their children seem clumsier than most and have trouble paying attention.   The target child still is having trouble with appetite so the mom makes an appointment after 4 weeks for a follow-up visit with the PNP. She shares the coincidences discovered in talking with other moms on the playground. As a PNP who understands principles of public health you identify which social and physical determinants of health that may be risk factors for health conditions with these combined health outcomes?   ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_42","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_42","title":"Public Health Outcomes: Describe population-health determinants of health Discuss how these factors influence health status and health care delivery ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide10008","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"Case Study","thumbnail":"","children":["si15875","si15886","si15892","si15905","si15919","si19309","Text_Caption_6","Text_Caption_34","Text_Caption_40","Text_Caption_41","Text_Caption_42"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":834},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide10008"}}},{"id":"si19320","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide10020q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19412","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"g ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide10020q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_27","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_27","title":"Population Health: Public Health ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_35","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_35","title":"4 / 8 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10061","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Based on the history from the mom at this 4 week follow-up visit, which social determinants of health are risk factors for this child? Select all that apply:  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10076","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10080","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Poor ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10080","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide10020q0"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si10076_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Poor\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si10087","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10091","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Member of a racial-ethnic minority group ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10091","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide10020q0"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si10087_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Member of a racial-ethnic minority group\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si19443","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19447","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Recent immigrant ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19447","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide10020q0"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si19443_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Recent immigrant\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si19458","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19462","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Live in older, poorly managed rental property ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19462","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide10020q0"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si19458_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Live in older, poorly managed rental property\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si19473","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19477","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Parents exposed at work  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19477","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide10020q0"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si19473_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Parents exposed at work \r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si10108","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide10020q0","for":"Slide10020q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10095","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide10020q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19481","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Correct - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide10020q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19494","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"The correct responses are A, B, and D. from the history in the case study we do not know this family’s immigration status nor whether the parents were exposed to toxins at work. Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide10020q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide10020","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si15875","si15886","si15892","si15905","si15919","si19320","si19412","Text_Caption_27","Text_Caption_35","si10061","si10080","si10091","si19447","si19462","si19477","si10108","si10095"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":396},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide10020"},"question":{"interactionId":"10048","quizId":380,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"Based on the history from the mom at this 4 week follow-up visit, which social determinants of health are risk factors for this child? Select all that apply:\r\r","ikc":true,"type":"knowledgeCheck","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["A","B","D"]}}},{"id":"si19622","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"g ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_26","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_26","title":"Link: CDC - Blood Test Safety Alert ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_28","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_28","title":"Population Health: Public Health ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_36","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_36","title":"5 / 8 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Web_1","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Web_1","roles":{}},{"id":"Text_Caption_43","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_43","title":"Click here if video does not load ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide9821","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"Health Status of Population","thumbnail":"","children":["si15875","si15886","si15892","si15905","si15919","si19622","Text_Caption_26","Text_Caption_28","Text_Caption_36","Text_Caption_43"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide9821"}}},{"id":"si19894","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide19893q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19905","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"g ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide19893q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_29","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_29","title":"Population Health: Public Health ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_37","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_37","title":"6 / 8 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19698","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_7","title":"Which signs and symptoms of lead toxicity has this child exhibited in recent visits? Select all that apply: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19709","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_12","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19713","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_13","title":"Developmental Delay ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19713","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"3","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide19893q1"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si19709_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"2","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Developmental Delay\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si19720","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_14","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19724","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_15","title":"Learning difficulties ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19724","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"5","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide19893q1"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si19720_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"4","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Learning difficulties\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si19731","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_16","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19735","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_17","title":"Irritability ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19735","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"7","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide19893q1"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si19731_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"6","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Irritability\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si19742","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_18","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19746","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_19","title":"Loss of appetite  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19746","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"9","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide19893q1"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si19742_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"8","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Loss of appetite \r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si19753","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_20","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19757","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_21","title":"Weight loss ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19757","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"11","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide19893q1"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si19753_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"10","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Weight loss\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si19949","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"F) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19953","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Sluggishness and fatigue ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19953","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide19893q1"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si19949_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Sluggishness and fatigue\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si19964","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"G) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19968","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Abdominal Pain ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19968","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide19893q1"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si19964_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Abdominal Pain\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si19979","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"H) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19983","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Vomiting ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19983","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide19893q1"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si19979_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Vomiting\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si19821","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_1","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide19893q1","for":"Slide19893q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19795","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_3","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide19893q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19852","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_4","title":"Correct - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide19893q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19883","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_5","title":"The correct responses are A, C, D, and E. We know there are subtle cognitive delays based on the development screen, but they are subtle and need to be reassessed before we determine the child has learning difficulties. There was no report by the mom that the child was sluggish or fatigued. The child is clumsy but this is not the same. There was no report of abdominal pain or vomiting. Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide19893q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide19893","class":"Question Slide","instance":"Knowledge Check 2","thumbnail":"","children":["si15875","si15886","si15892","si15905","si15919","si19894","si19905","Text_Caption_29","Text_Caption_37","si19698","si19713","si19724","si19735","si19746","si19757","si19953","si19968","si19983","si19821","si19795"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":642},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide19893"},"question":{"interactionId":"19675","quizId":380,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"Which signs and symptoms of lead toxicity has this child exhibited in recent visits? Select all that apply:\r","ikc":true,"type":"knowledgeCheck","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["A","C","D","E"]}}},{"id":"si19999","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"g ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_30","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_30","title":"Population Health: Public Health ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_38","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_38","title":"7 / 8 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_45","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_45","title":"Click here if video does not load ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Web_3","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Web_3","roles":{}},{"id":"Slide19998","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"Public Health Oriented NP Actions","thumbnail":"","children":["si15875","si15886","si15892","si15905","si15919","si19999","Text_Caption_30","Text_Caption_38","Text_Caption_45"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide19998"}}},{"id":"si20163","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"g ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_4","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_4","roles":{}},{"id":"SmartShape_6","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_6","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_22","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_22","title":"Thank you for completing the Public Health sub-module! ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_7","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_7","title":"Click here to exit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20124","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Click here to exit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20144","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Click here to exit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_23","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_23","title":"-or- ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_24","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_24","title":"Click here to begin the next sub-module ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_31","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_31","title":"Population Health: Public Health ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_39","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_39","title":"8 / 8 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide20010","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si15875","si15886","si15892","si15905","si15919","si20163","Image_4","SmartShape_6","Text_Caption_22","SmartShape_7","si20124","si20144","Text_Caption_23","Text_Caption_24","Text_Caption_31","Text_Caption_39"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide20010"}}},{"id":"Pool424","class":"pool","roles":{"pool":{"id":424,"name":"Pool1","questions":[]}}},{"id":"Pop_Health_Public Health","class":"project","title":"Pop_Health_Public Health","children":["Slide9971","Slide5186","Slide10008","Slide10020","Slide9821","Slide19893","Slide19998","Slide20010"],"roles":{"quiz":{"id":380,"branched":false,"submitAll":false,"review":true,"questions":["Slide10020q0","Slide19893q1"],"minScore":0,"maxScore":0,"passScore":0}}}],"contentSettings":{"global":{"branchAware":false},"toc":{"navigationEnabled":true,"navigateVisitedSlides":false,"collapseAll":false,"showTopicDuration":false,"statusFlag":true,"selfPaced":true,"showSearch":false,"enabled":true},"playbar":{"enabled":false,"cc":false,"playPause":true,"back":true,"forward":true,"rewind":true,"close":true,"mute":true,"progressBar":true}},"contentReporting":{"CCCriteria":"launch_content","SCCriteria":"launch_content","exitNormalIfCompleted":false},"toc":[{"id":"Slide9971","title":"Slide 1","visible":false},{"id":"Slide5186","title":"Public Health Definition","visible":true},{"id":"Slide10008","title":"Case Study","visible":true},{"id":"Slide10020","title":"Slide 4","visible":false},{"id":"Slide9821","title":"Health Status of Population","visible":true},{"id":"Slide19893","title":"Knowledge Check 2","visible":false},{"id":"Slide19998","title":"Public Health Oriented NP Actions","visible":true},{"id":"Slide20010","title":"Slide 8","visible":false}]}